<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<search>
  <total_items>158</total_items>
  <page_size>20</page_size>
  <page_count>8</page_count>
  <page_number>1</page_number>
  <page_items></page_items>
  <first_item></first_item>
  <last_item></last_item>
  <search_time>0.991</search_time>
  <events>
    <event id="E0-001-089593997-0">
      <title>Dressing Strip in Ireland at SafetyDirect</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/dressing-strip-ireland-safetydirect-/E0-001-089593997-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description>Safety Direct offers Dressing Strip from established brands like Mascot, North, 3M and Dependable. They are well suited for home, restaurant, hotel or workplace use. They have an assortment of items for treating everyday injuries as well. They have alcohol wipes, non-adhesive pads and medical dressings. Browse online at Safety Direct and pick one of your preferred objects - Dressing Strip is composed of an absorbent, low adherent wound pad backed by a high quality stretch fabric, which is presented in a dispenser box. With the widths available, dressings can be cut to desired shape and size.For over 20 years SafetyDirect have been making plasters and their Dressing Strip are ideal for when a tough plaster is required. The fabric strip has a strong adhesion to keeps wounds, cuts and grazes dry. Dressing Strip have been especially designed to protect wounds around joints, elbows and knees. The long dressing strip can be cut to size to suit a variety of wounds, cuts and grazes - Dressing Strip.Check Out our Stock on Dressing Strip in Ireland :Phone : +35391745150Email : sales@safetydirect(dot)ieWeb URL : https://www.safetydirect.ie/6748/Reliance-Dependaplast-Washproof-Dressing-Strip/product.aspx</description>
      <start_time>2015-12-12 10:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2017-09-27 21:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009748380-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/ireland-/V0-001-009748380-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Ireland</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Ireland</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2015-12-11 02:39:50</created>
      <owner>uniiverse</owner>
      <modified>2015-12-11 02:40:05</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-091300965-0@2016031418">
      <title>Matchbook Trader Workshops</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/matchbook-trader-workshops-/E0-001-091300965-0@2016031418?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Workshop Series More Insight | Interaction | Networking The Matchbook Traders Conference, held this past October in London, was a smashing hit - 9 in 10 delegates would recommend the event to a friend! To build on this event, we reviewed the constructive feedback we received from delegates: “Attempted to pack too many speakers into the agenda leaving little time for questions, interactions, in depth analysis. Not enough networking time.” “Less speakers and more insight.” “Lack of breakout sessions.” Your feedback, and our desire to nuture this vibrant community, has inspired us to launch The Matchbook Trader Workshops - a series of in-depth workshops covering a diverse range of topics from the conference and beyond. smaller groups (50 or less) more insight and analysis and of course, more time for networking! The same spirit and fun as the Matchbook Traders Conference condensed into 1 evening of accelerated learning.      Next Workshop Sports Betting To Win  Practical Strategies For Enhanced Decision Making, Discipline and Performance.   Success in sports betting requires more than skill and an effective betting strategy; you also need to master the inner-game!  Join us on March 14th and delve into the psychology of trading with Steve Ward. We&amp;#39;ll discuss how best to manage your emotions, master your mind, and overcome the urges and temptations to deviate away from your plan. In this seminar, leading trading performance and psychology coach Steve Ward, will provide practical tips and strategies drawn from performance psychology, neuroscience, decision science, stress physiology and mindfulness based approaches to help you enhance your decision making process, strengthen your discipline and improve your betting performance.   Steve will cover: The 3 keys to becoming a successful sports bettor The high performance sports betting cycle Preparation – getting ready to perform The 5 keys to effective execution and strengthening discipline Developing attention, willpower and discipline Managing emotions Dealing with pressure and stress, and betting with poise The mind-body connection, energy and decision fatigue Evaluation, analysis and continual improvement   About our Speaker   Steve Ward  Steve specializes in coaching, training and developing people and teams in risk-taking, high pressure, results-driven environments, helping them to develop the performance and psychological skills to achieve and sustain high performance. He has over 20 years of experience, starting in sports and performance psychology with elite athletes and teams in over 30 different sports before specializing with traders in 2005. His clients include leading investment banks, investment managers, energy companies and proprietary trading groups across the globe.     Steve is the author of High Performance Trading, TraderMind and Sports Betting To Win and was a consultant on the BBC TV documentary Million Dollar Traders.       Topics for the remaining 2 workshops will be announced on March 14th If you&amp;#39;d like to see a specific topic covered, please drop us a suggestion at:  http://goo.gl/forms/a9cIp2QJBO     </description>
      <start_time>2016-03-14 18:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-000235001-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/london-united-kingdom-/V0-001-000235001-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>London, United Kingdom</venue_name>
      <venue_display>0</venue_display>
      <venue_address>London, United Kingdom</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code>SW1</postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5112139</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1198244</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until November 14, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-02-21 07:47:53</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-03-03 08:19:37</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-091126904-5@2016042709">
      <title>Leadership and Management Training</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/leadership-and-management-/E0-001-091126904-5@2016042709?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Cost: &lt;strong&gt; £1,020.00 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;em&gt;leadership and management training course&lt;/em&gt; is designed to help you to&lt;em&gt; gain more confidence&lt;/em&gt; by showing you exactly how to achieve your goals and keep your priorities in order.&lt;p&gt;Our trainers will show you &lt;em&gt;practical methods&lt;/em&gt; to help you become more effective and confident. The purpose of the training is to&lt;em&gt; improve performance&lt;/em&gt; and create a friendly and productive working atmosphere. The core objective of this comprehensive training course is to enable leaders to set and achieve organisational and personal goals, by communicating clearly with their teams, managing time more effectively and prioritising work.&lt;p&gt;The course will also cover the most effective ways to manage conflict and handle difficult people. Managers participating in this course will be able to create and sustain a &lt;em&gt;positive mental attitude&lt;/em&gt; and inspire their teams to be productive and creative.&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 1 - Morning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How can you get the best from yourself and others&lt;li&gt;How to set and achieve realistic goals&lt;li&gt;More accurate communication&lt;li&gt;Better listening skills&lt;li&gt;How to explain your ideas with more confidence&lt;li&gt;Distinguish between the cynic and the critic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 1 - Afternoon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Handling difficult people and conflict situations&lt;li&gt;Assertiveness&lt;li&gt;How to speak in factual language not emotional language&lt;li&gt;Distinguish reasons from excuses &lt;li&gt;When to compromise and when not to&lt;li&gt;How to distinguish between aggressive, passive and assertive communication&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 2 - Morning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time management&lt;li&gt;Distinguish busy vs. productive activity&lt;li&gt;Planning ahead&lt;li&gt;Proper delegation&lt;li&gt;Prioritisation&lt;li&gt;Decision matrix&lt;li&gt;Law of diminishing returns&lt;li&gt;Problem cause solution mental mapping&lt;li&gt;Pareto principle 80/20 rule&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 2 - Afternoon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to create a productive office atmosphere&lt;li&gt;Creating more goal focused action&lt;li&gt;Success formula: Purpose, Plan, Action, Feedback, Change·   &lt;li&gt;Final summary and action planning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This training course in leadership and management development is designed for anyone who needs to get the best from themselves and other people, and is beneficial for:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Non-managers&lt;li&gt;First time managers&lt;li&gt;Supervisors&lt;li&gt;Front line manager&lt;li&gt;Middle managers&lt;li&gt;Senior managers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-04-27 09:30:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-000235001-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/london-united-kingdom-/V0-001-000235001-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>London, United Kingdom</venue_name>
      <venue_display>0</venue_display>
      <venue_address>London, United Kingdom</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code>SW1</postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5112139</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1198244</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>on various days</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-02-13 17:22:50</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-04-23 03:07:57</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-089980917-2@2016052518">
      <title>Start-ups' pitch in front of Investors</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/startups-pitch-front-inves-/E0-001-089980917-2@2016052518?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Spaces are limited and we usually get good turn outs at our events. Doors open at 6pm for networking, and the programme starts at 7.15pm. Please pay £2 fee at the door. Start: 6 pm, this is networking time until 7:15 pm. From 7:15 to 7:30 pm, introduction.  From 7:30 pm to 8:45 pm: 5 fifteen Minutes Business Sales Pitches in front of possible investors will be presented at this time. If interested in these 15 minutes sales pitch then please email irfan@heptagonevents.com for further details and booking. At this platform an Investment penal is ready to finance reliable start-ups. From 8:45 pm till 10:00 pm: Networking again. Why to attend? Answer: 1) To raise finance or find investment opportunities; 2) To witness the start-ups&amp;#39; pitch and Investors&amp;#39; questions; 3) To network; 4) To learn Networking skills; 5) To relax and have a chat; 6) To learn as to what others are doing; 7) To build or to retain old connections. </description>
      <start_time>2016-05-25 18:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009107449-1</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/worklife-/V0-001-009107449-1?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>WORKLIFE</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>13 Hawley Crescent , Camden</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>on various days</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2015-12-30 06:20:43</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2015-12-30 06:20:43</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-090085168-2@2016060108">
      <title>Terminal 3, Travel and Work Remotey</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/terminal-3-travel-and-work-/E0-001-090085168-2@2016060108?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Travel and Work Remotely for Six Months in Six Countries Terminal 3 takes a group of people to Travel, Work and Explore, In six months we visit six countries, spending a month at each. The group will consist of remote workers, startups, freelancers and anyone with the flexibility to take their job on the road. When Terminal 3 launches in June 2016 Where June - Lisbon, Portugal July - Morocco  August - Istanbul, Turkey September - Seoul, South Korea October - Hanoi, Vietnam November - Cape Town, South Africa The above provisional itinerary may be subject to change. Who Terminal 3 is aimed at: Digital nomads Freelancers Startups Entrepreneurs Anyone with a remote job Anyone who has a job, why not ask your manager if you can work remotely! Agenda For a monthly payment of £1,200 you get: Central Accommodation Central cowork space Weekly yoga classes Weekly language classes Travel between all destinations  Local impact days    and much more! NB: Once accepted a payment of £2,000 will secure your spot, places are limited! Applications are now open! Click here to apply and join a group of like minded people travelling and work remotely across the world. WE TRAVEL not to escape life BUT FOR LIFE not to escape us For any questions please contact hola@terminal3.co Stay connected on Facebook and Twitter #T3BORDERLESS </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-01 08:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-005835833-2</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/london-/V0-001-005835833-2?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>London</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>48 Oxford Street London W1D 1BF</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5163604</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1325915</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until December 1, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-01-05 08:36:00</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-06-17 00:05:07</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-089559552-7@2016060118">
      <title>A Year of Nurture Network 2016/2017</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/year-nurture-network-20162-/E0-001-089559552-7@2016060118?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> What is Nurture Network? Membership to the Nurture Network includes 11 two-hour networking events, taking place once per month at the beautiful October Gallery in Russell Square. Each two-hour meeting will be strengths-based and solution-focused. These will be facilitated sessions that will concentrate on celebrating your success and growth.   There will plenty of opportunity to network with other members and build supportive alliances.   By joining Nurture Network, you will: Receive the support of a generous, supportive community of women. Relate to yourself as your ‘best self’… be inspired by her!  Retire old and worn out versions of your former self. Respect yourself and grow yourself to a whole new level. Reach your goals, with a new found confidence. Renew and refresh yourself with a community you can trust.   When is the Nurture Network? From 7pm - 9pm at October Gallery, Russell Square, Central London, on Wednesdays...   Starting 1st June 2016 and continuing 6th July ~ 7th September 5th October ~ 2nd November 7th December ~ 11th January 2017 1st February ~ 1st March 5th April ~ 3rd May     Why not purchase a Nurture Network 2016/2017 + Immersion Experience ticket and join one of our Immersion Experience events in 2016 for just £100.   Find out more... The Immersion Experience - April 2016 The Immersion Experience - May 2016     </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-01 18:30:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-001056699-3</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/october-gallery-/V0-001-001056699-3?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>October Gallery</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>24 Old Gloucester Street</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code>WC1N</postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5206544</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1218418</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until May 3, 2017</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2015-12-09 05:26:21</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-04-19 11:45:35</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-093496008-2@2016060319">
      <title>Digital money / Cryptocurrency - Use, invest, share &amp; earn. London</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/digital-money-cryptocurre-/E0-001-093496008-2@2016060319?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Digital money / Cryptocurrency  It is NOT the Money for the Internet - It is the Internet for the Money! This is an opportunity for EVERYONE, EVERYWHERE. View the video http://bit.ly/OneCoin_Presentation (English + 13 other languages) Sign up for FREE http://bit.ly/onecoin_global Explore and learn how to invest, share, earn, profit and benefit from the digital money revolution of OneCoin CryptoCurrency &amp; BlockChain. You will get a professional online backoffice office with education, tools and products for your own investment and if you like also for commision sales of OneCoin CryptoCurrency and BlockChain Subscribe to YouTube Channel http://bit.ly/OneCoin_YouTube Follow us at Twitter http://bit.ly/OneCoin_Twitter Like us at Facebook http://bit.ly/OneCoin_Facebook Register to create your own events http://www.eventbrite.com/r/onecoin - No set up or &amp;quot;subscribtion&amp;quot; fees. - Free for free events - By % on sales on paid events. </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-03 19:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-007195536-5</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/your-computer-/V0-001-007195536-5?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Your Computer</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address></venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until July 4, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-05-19 05:35:40</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-05-24 03:55:29</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-090135652-8@2016060409">
      <title>Developing Middle Leaders</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/developing-middle-leaders-/E0-001-090135652-8@2016060409?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> A professional leadership development programme for experienced middle leaders delivered by the Institute of Education. Are you a middle leader responsible for leading a team of staff with some experience of the role - then this is the programme for you. This innovative programme will help you develop your confidence and leadership skills. It will enable you to improve your ability to lead and manage change.  The programme is delivered over 3 days with inter-sessional tasks for participants to complete including a small scale action research project. There is an option to use this programme to gain 30 Master’s Credits towards an MA.  Programme dates Day 1 21 March 2016 (09:30 –16:00) Day 2 16 May 2016 (09:30 –16:00) Day 3 14 June 2016 (09:30 –16.00) Twilight Session 5 July 2016 (13:00-16:00) </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-04 09:30:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009274063-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/woodfield-teaching-school-alliance-/V0-001-009274063-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Woodfield Teaching School Alliance</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Glenwood Avenue</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until July 5, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-01-07 07:58:10</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-02-04 15:21:36</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-092971727-3@2016061010">
      <title>Accelerator Course for Freelancers - London</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/accelerator-course-freelan-/E0-001-092971727-3@2016061010?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> We are collaborating with one of London&amp;#39;s most desirable coworking spaces, Huckletree, to bring you our Accelerator Course for Freelancers. Full details about the content and structure of this course can be found here: Accelerator Course for Freelancers Dates &amp; Times: Monday 6th June - 10am-2pm Monday 13th June - 10am-2pm Monday 20th June - 10am-2pm Monday 27th June - 10am-2pm Monday 4th July - 10am-2pm Monday 11th July - 10am-2pm Location: Huckletree, Alphabeta Building, 18 Finsbury Square, London Duration: 6 weeks For all enquiries: hello@wildfolkclassroom.com We offer a payment plan option as well as the ticket options below. To arrange your payment plan please email us at: hello@wildfolkclassroom.com Ticket prices include a light lunch and all other refreshments.  </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-10 10:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009844448-6</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/opentable-/V0-001-009844448-6?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>OpenTable</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Alphabeta Building , 14-18 Finsbury Square</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until July 11, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-04-26 12:32:12</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-06-17 00:20:02</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-089376946-5@2016061110">
      <title>Business Skills - How to Run an Effective Practice</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/business-skills-run-effec-/E0-001-089376946-5@2016061110?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Book your place on the entire Business Skills CPD series - 4 days, 10 hours of CPD 5 April - Effective Marketing: Grow Your Business with a Digital Strategy Hone your brand message - to get noticed for your clear online presence. 3-4 May - The Essentials of Starting a Practice (2 days) Over the course of two mornings, this 5-hour two-part seminar will give a clear introduction to the key aspects of starting your own architecture practice.  12 July - Effective Team Working &amp; The Psychology of Performance This session will enable you to determine what it takes in a modern, connected world for teams and team members to create sustainable high performance.  Booking a place at all 4 CPD seminars saves you over £30 Terms &amp; Conditions Cancellations for pay-as-you-go tickets are permitted up to 10 working days before the event, delegate substitutions are accepted at any time, please contact cpdlondon@riba.org for cancellation/substitution requests. An email will be sent to confirm your place on receipt of your booking.  A second email confirming venue along with map/directions will be sent to you approx. 7-10 days before the event. Bookings at the member rates will only be accepted if accompanied by a valid membership number. If you require a purchase order to be quoted on your invoice this must be supplied at the time of booking. </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-11 10:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009720680-7</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/arper-/V0-001-009720680-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Arper</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>11 Clerkenwell Road</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until July 12, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2015-12-03 13:40:33</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-04-08 08:48:03</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-070550299-0">
      <title>Taste of London</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/taste-london-/E0-001-070550299-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Taste of London is happening on 15 Jun 2016 at Regents Park London, United Kingdom. Its a premier event in Food &amp; Beverage industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://login.10times.com/stall-book/135391" rel="nofollow"&gt;Book a stall at 10times.com!&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-15 00:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-19 00:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-006084604-3</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/regents-park-/V0-001-006084604-3?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Regents Park</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Gloucester Green</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>2</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2014-05-09 11:44:23</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-01-23 18:28:04</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>conference</id>
          <name>Conferences &amp;amp; Tradeshows</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-092659693-4@2016061514">
      <title>Trees in Hard Landscapes seminars - Reimagining streets for greater sustainability: the role of trees</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/trees-hard-landscapes-semi-/E0-001-092659693-4@2016061514?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> A two-part cross-disciplinary exploration of the latest research, technical solutions and project examples for the contemporary use of trees in streets and the wider public realm.     Working in close collaboration with engineers and other allied professions, landscape architects have a central role to play in re-imagining street design to enhance the sustainability, resilience and liveability of towns and cities.   The fundamental principles of Manual for Streets and Manual for Streets 2 in England and Designing Streets in Scotland are i) the creation of better places and ii) encouraging and providing for people to walk, cycle and use public transport. Performance specifications for the public realm are also increasingly shaped by the need to adapt to on-going climate changes, particularly in respect to surface water management. How can landscape elements, and especially trees, contribute to these objectives? Where are some good examples? What are the key success factors and technical solutions design professionals should be aware of?   Two half-day seminars combining presentations and debates will explore these questions, drawing from the content of the Trees and Design Action Group latest publication: Trees in Hard Landscapes: A Guide for Delivery (2014, 164pp). The guide is available as a free download at www.tdag.org.uk A professionally printed and bound hardcopy can also be ordered when booking for the seminar.     SeMINAR 1: Wed 15 June 2016 from 2.00pm to 5.15pm From roads to safer, better streets – using trees to empower sustainable transport solutions The fundamental principles of Manual for Streets and Manual for Streets 2 in England and Designing Streets in Scotland are i) the creation of better places and ii) encouraging and providing for people to walk, cycle and use public transport. Landscape elements, especially trees, have a critical role to play in contemporary approaches to street design where reduced separation, contextual (rather than standardized) solutions and a more human scale responding to desire lines provide a basis to achieve lower vehicular speeds and increased user awareness as well as a more attractive environment where people want to spend their time.   Rich with insights from civil and highways engineers as well as a tree specialist with a strong track record in working creatively with street trees, this seminar will explore the evidence base demonstrating the relevance of such approaches, the ways-of-working it requires, as well as the above and below ground solutions available to make it a lasting success. It will be relevant to designers working on contemporary streetscape projects and transport professionals involved in sustainable transport plans delivery.   CHAIR: Robert Huxford, Director, Urban Design Group Robert is Director of the Urban Design Group, co-founder of the Public Realm Information and Advice Network (PRIAN), and a member of the Institution of Civil Engineers’ Municipal Expert Panel. He lectures in Highway Law and Liability, and broader public realm topics and will be the lead author of the upcoming 3rd ed. of the UK Guide on Highway Risk and Liability Claims.   SPEAKERS TO INCLUDE: Rupert Bentley-Walls, Director, EcoArb [bio forthcoming]   Anne Jaluzot, Green infrastructure planning consultant Anne is an urban planner, with 13 years of experience primarily gathered in the US and the UK in environmentally led approaches to urban policy, design and regeneration. She has worked for the City of Chicago supporting the development, implementation and monitoring of the City’s innovative urban greening programmes. In the UK, as part of the Commission for Architecture and the Built Environment (CABE), she has led CABE Space’s input into a wide range of local green infrastructure planning initiatives and associated national knowledge building and policy efforts. Anne now works as an independent consultant continuing to advise on, assess, facilitate or lead the development of tools, strategies, projects and knowledge on urban greening. This brought her to conduct the research and writing of the Trees and Design Action Group (TDAG)’s two latest publications: Trees in the Townscape: A Guide for Decision Makers (2012) and Trees in Hard Landscapes: A Guide for Delivery (2014) – two action-oriented urban forestry best practice guides on using trees in 21st century cities.   Paul Morris, Senior Associate, Civic Engineers Associate Director at Civic Engineers (previously Stockley), Paul is an expert in the design and delivery of high specification structural engineering projects, development appraisal and infrastructure strategies as well as highways, public realm and drainage design. Paul has also worked with “Places Matter!” to deliver a series of workshops on the implementation of Manual for Streets.   Prof. Alan Simson, Leeds Metropolitan University Professor Alan Simson is a chartered landscape architect, urban forester and urban designer.  He has gained extensive professional experience in the UK New Towns, private practice and higher education. Currently, he is Professor of Landscape Architecture + Urban Forestry at Leeds Beckett University, where he is involved in research, teaching and consultancy on urban futures and landscape urbanism, both in the UK and abroad.   He has led several European urban forestry research projects on behalf of the UK, such as COST Action E12 Urban Forests and Trees and the EU’s NeighbourWoods project, and is involved in a number of international, national and regional initiatives / activities, including COST FP 1204 GreenInUrbs.  He is a member of the European Forum on Urban Forestry and represented the UK at the 1st Asian - Pacific meeting on Urban Forestry in China. He’s a member of the LI’s Biosecurity Group and chair of their Urban Forestry Initiative. He also chairs the White Rose Forest and is a Trustee / Director of the Community Forest Trust.       Seminar 2: Wed 22 June 2016 from 2.00pm to 5.15pm SuDS in the public realm – making the most of trees   Performance specifications for the public realm are increasingly shaped by the need to adapt to on-going climate changes, particularly in respect to water management. With often over 100 hectares of surfaces available for water interception, absorption or evapotranspiration, a well-integrated street tree has a lot to offer to water sensitive urban design. Across Greater Lyon in France, an area which has adopted ambitious objectives for the systematic use of sustainable drainage public realm projects, trees are an integral part of the solution. In the UK, the latest edition of the SuDS Manual by CIRIA now includes a chapter exclusively dedicated to trees, and an increasing number of local authorities and infrastructure managers – including water companies – are trialing designs that use trees and their rooting environment to create attractive, safe and water resilient streetscapes.   At a time when Transport for London has commissioned a SuDS Guidance for the capital’s red routes, this seminar will explore some of the key principles, available technical solution and inspiring examples of collaboration between green and grey professions around streets, SuDS and trees. It will be particularly relevant to designers working on contemporary streetscape projects as well as sustainability and drainage specialists involved in flood risks prevention and sustainable water management.   CHAIR: Sue Illman, Director, Illman-Young and Past President of the Landscape Institute Sue is currently Managing Director of Illman Young, and initiated their interest in the sustainable use of water in 2005.  Since then, the practice has developed a specialism in integrated SuDS design and Water Sensitive Urban Design (WSUD).  Illman Young are supporters of Susdrain and Sue has been part of its project steering committee as well as the WSUD (Water Sensitive Urban Design) steering group.  She is co-author of the new SuDS Manual for CIRIA. She has also contributed to Developer Guidelines - Integrated Sustainable Design Solutions for Modular Neighbourhoods, published by NHDC. She is a regular lecturer on the integrated design of SuDS and has run a wide range of training courses on the subject.  She has recently sat as a member of the All Party Parliamentary Group for Excellence in the Built Environment’s Inquiry into Flooding and Resilience, and has been heavily involved in writing the finished report. Sue Illman has also been appointed as CIC Champion for Flood Mitigation and Resilience.     SPEAKERS TO INCLUDE: Owen Davies, Flood Risk Manager, Royal Borough of Greenwich Owen Davies is currently Flood risk Manager for the Royal Borough of Greenwich, with responsibility in responding to the Flood and Water Management Act, ensuring legislative requirements are met and introducing relevant polices and strategies to manage and where appropriate mitigate flood risk using a wide range of tools, including SuDS and GI. With 18 years’ experience working in Local Government across four central London boroughs, with a focus on Highways from network management to award winning public realm improvements ranging from Crime reduction, Accessibility, Road Safety through to recently SuDS and Green Infrastructure. Alongside introduction of policies such as Network management, temporary structures and Asset management.   Martin Gammie, Director, Consulting with Trees Martin has dedicated his career to the world of forestry, landscape and arboriculture over the past 30 years. His consultancy practice, Consulting with Trees Ltd. focuses on innovative design and working practices that facilitate effective establishment and compatible longevity of trees in the urban environment. Promoting his industry and improving professionalism within it is at the heart of Martin’s work. He is an active member of the Trees and Design Action Group (TDAG), has established the first Tree Warden scheme in Oxfordshire and launched the South Oxfordshire Arboricultural Industry Forum. Most recently Martin has become a founding trustee of the charity Fund4Trees which seeks to raise funds for tree related research and educational material. Martin is a Chartered Forester and Fellow of the Arboricultural Association.   Anne Jaluzot, Green infrastructure planning consultant Anne is an urban planner, with 13 years of experience primarily gathered in the US and the UK in environmentally led approaches to urban policy, design and regeneration. She has worked for the City of Chicago supporting the development, implementation and monitoring of the City’s innovative urban greening programmes. In the UK, as part of the Commission for Architecture and the Built Environment (CABE), she has led CABE Space’s input into a wide range of local green infrastructure planning initiatives and associated national knowledge building and policy efforts. Anne now works as an independent consultant continuing to advise on, assess, facilitate or lead the development of tools, strategies, projects and knowledge on urban greening. This brought her to conduct the research and writing of the Trees and Design Action Group (TDAG)’s two latest publications: Trees in the Townscape: A Guide for Decision Makers (2012) and Trees in Hard Landscapes: A Guide for Delivery (2014) – two action-oriented urban forestry best practice guides on using trees in 21st century cities.   Stephen O&amp;#39;Malley, Director, Civic Engineers Previously a shareholding director at Stockley, Stephen was one of the founding directors of Civic Engineers in 2009. This practice has since completed and continues to deliver high quality civil, structural and urban infrastructure projects. Stephen has a passion for and a belief in the importance of public realm and place making, using design techniques and methods that rely on showcasing the prevailing character, culture and geography of the existing landscape and place, changing how people respond and engage with spaces. Stephen became a fellow of the Institute of Civil Engineers in 2013 and a Member of the CIHT in 2014. In 2014 Stephen led on the Practice’s appointment to the GLA’s Specialist Assistance Team, which was assembled to help London authorities shape and inform funding bids for capital projects particularly high street regeneration schemes. Stephen was appointed as a member to Architecture + Design Scotland Design Forum Panel in 2014. Since January 2016, Civic Engineers has also been appointed alongside J&amp;L Gibbons to produce the first SuDS Guidance Transport for London.       FAQs Is my registration/ticket transferrable? Name changes are permitted until until 4 working days before the event - 9th June 2016 What is the refund policy? Early Bird registrations are refundable until 7 days before the event - 8th June 2016 Standard registrations are non refundable.   Cancellation Policy:  Notice of cancellation must be made in writing to: Landscape Institute 107 Grays Inn Road, London, WC1X 8TZ. 21 days&amp;#39; notice or more before the event full refund given, less than 20 days notice, no refund given. Name changes permitted. Written notice should be sent to: Landscape Institute 107 Grays Inn Road, London, WC1X 8TZ Email:LaurenT@landscapeinstitute.org Data Protection: Landscape Institute may from time to time send information to those who registered for the conference about other events and related products or services. Landscape Institute, 107 Grays Inn Road, London, WC1X 8TZ www.landscapeinstitute.org Tel: 020 7685 2640 </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-15 14:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009641082-9</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/marshalls-design-space-/V0-001-009641082-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Marshalls Design Space</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Unit 4 Compton Courtyard</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>daily until June 22, 2016</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-04-13 16:08:41</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-06-09 04:37:53</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-093840297-5@2016061801">
      <title>Secure On Site company will be having a Master class</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/secure-site-company-will-h-/E0-001-093840297-5@2016061801?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description>Secure On Site company will be having a Master class Tour on June 15-19, 2016. If you are one of Secure On Site property clients who wants to get the best information in this field, this event is perfect for you. You will have a great chance to be provide highly skilled, knowledgeable industry professionals and revolutionary technology that assists the service at a competitive prices.</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-18 01:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-18 22:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-005495053-0</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/central-london-/V0-001-005495053-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Central London</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>route TBA TBA</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string>weekly on Tuesdays and Saturdays for 1 times</recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-06-02 14:18:03</created>
      <owner>secureonsite38ce6</owner>
      <modified>2016-06-02 17:03:54</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-093043433-0">
      <title>TV Jobs UK One Day Intensive TV &amp; Film Career Masterclass - Training &amp; Q&amp;A in London, June 18th 2016</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/tv-jobs-uk-one-day-intensive-tv-film-career-mast-/E0-001-093043433-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description>One Day Intensive TV &amp; Film Career Masterclass - Training &amp; Q&amp;A
Saturday June 18th 2016  10:30 - 15:30
Are you currently finding it difficult to get into the film or television industry or maybe you have recently graduated, in another career, or have done loads of unpaid work and you are looking for extra knowledge to help you get your foot in the door and get paid work
TV Jobs UK are holding an interactive and informative TV &amp; Film employability masterclass combining training and talks and a Q&amp;A with industry professionals, for those determined to make a mark within the industry. We will equip you with the know how of what you need to do find jobs and get paid work.
The masterclass will empower and equip learners with the skills in order to apply effectively to entry level roles within the industry.
Subjects covered include:
Understanding the job market.  
Online Job search  
Job search management.    
Networking  
Understanding Entry Roles  
CV writing and Cover letters  
Interview techniques  
Personal and Professional Attributes</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-18 10:30:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-18 15:30:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-008268435-7</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/canada-water-culture-space-/V0-001-008268435-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Canada Water Culture Space</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>21 Surrey Quays Road</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-04-30 20:51:29</created>
      <owner>Georgina2877c</owner>
      <modified>2016-05-09 16:07:45</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>conference</id>
          <name>Conferences &amp;amp; Tradeshows</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>movies_film</id>
          <name>Film</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-080973730-6">
      <title>City Fair</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/city-fair-/E0-001-080973730-6?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> City Fair is happening on 19 Jun 2016 at Wembley Stadium London, United Kingdom. Its a premier event in Travel &amp; Tourism industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://login.10times.com/stall-book/225081" rel="nofollow"&gt;Book a stall at 10times.com!&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-19 00:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-21 00:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-001023739-2</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/wembley-stadium-/V0-001-001023739-2?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Wembley Stadium</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>Wembley Park</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5560208</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.2795187</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>2</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2015-03-01 09:50:15</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2015-12-26 11:02:47</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>conference</id>
          <name>Conferences &amp;amp; Tradeshows</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-070727119-1">
      <title>Meter Asset Management</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/meter-asset-management-/E0-001-070727119-1?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Meter Asset Management is happening on 20 Jun 2016 at Hotel Holiday Inn Kensington Forum London, United Kingdom. Its a premier event in Business Services industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://login.10times.com/stall-book/137715" rel="nofollow"&gt;Book a stall at 10times.com!&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-20 00:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-21 00:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-005763920-3</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/marriott-regents-park-/V0-001-005763920-3?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Marriott Regents Park</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>22 Hertsmere Road</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5075140</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.0211360</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>2</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2014-05-17 10:24:16</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-03-05 12:01:12</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>conference</id>
          <name>Conferences &amp;amp; Tradeshows</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-092071468-0">
      <title>Mens Health</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/mens-health-/E0-001-092071468-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Mens Health is happening on 20 Jun 2016 at Royal College of General Practitioners London, United Kingdom. Its a premier event in Medical &amp; Pharmaceutical industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://login.10times.com/stall-book/123708" rel="nofollow"&gt;Book a stall at 10times.com!&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-20 00:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time>2016-06-20 00:00:00</stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-006679582-0</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/royal-college-of-general-practitioners-/V0-001-006679582-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Royal College of General Practitioners</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>30 Euston Square</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5275080</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1309443</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>2</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-03-20 07:16:50</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-03-20 07:16:50</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>conference</id>
          <name>Conferences &amp;amp; Tradeshows</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>support</id>
          <name>Health &amp;amp; Wellness</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>outdoors_recreation</id>
          <name>Outdoors &amp;amp; Recreation</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-090087730-7">
      <title>Project Preparation for Renewable Energy Projects in Africa: London, UK</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/project-preparation-renewable-energy-projects-afr-/E0-001-090087730-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> The Project Preparation seminar is an introduction to the project development process, walking participant through the key elements, activities, and processes. It is particularly helpful for projects that are just an idea or in the early stages. It is suitable for government agencies, private sector, communities, developers, technical teams, and technical support agencies. The seminar, and other options, is also excellent for building holistic capacity in organizations that develop and/or support projects in Africa. Developing renewable energy projects is not just a technical task, but involves a full range of elements to develop a sustainable business model. This business model takes into account ownership structure, communities, understanding requirements for funding, capacity, technology, financial models, environmental and market analysis, etc. Project developers, and their stakeholders, regularly find a heavier burden to bring all the necessary pieces together for projects in Africa. Many project developers find that having the technical capacity and/or connections is not sufficient to develop a bankable project. The Afribiz Foundation is offering this seminar as a part of its Developing and Structuring Bankable Projects in Africa initiative, which provides capacity building, technical assistance, and funding for early to middle stage projects. Seminar Modules The following are the modules in Project Preparation: Introduction and Key Components of Projects Project Development Process and Project Definition Developing and Managing Projects: Idea to Concept Developing and Managing Projects: Concept to Prefeasibility Developing and Managing Projects: Prefeasibility to Feasibility Leveraging Key Stakeholders, Networks, and Value Chains Developing Project Ecosystems &amp; Partnerships Developing and Managing Projects: Feasibility to Funding The take-home seminar materials include templates for Project Definition and Concept Document. Strategic Partners   </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-20 08:30:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009795551-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/nixon-peabody-/V0-001-009795551-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Nixon Peabody</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>International House , 21 Hanover Street</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-01-05 09:43:05</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-01-05 09:43:05</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
        <category>
          <id>politics_activism</id>
          <name>Politics &amp;amp; Activism</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-092735605-0">
      <title>Goal Setting Training Course</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/goal-setting-training-course-/E0-001-092735605-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Cost: &lt;strong&gt; £522.00 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the end of the course, you will develop a S.M.A.R.T goal focus and will be able to communicate your aims more confidently. You will be able to quantify your goals and outcomes, as well as to verbally define them.&lt;p&gt;In addition, this course develops your leadership abilities and performance management skills, so that you&amp;#39;ll be able to give practical feedback to those people who are not performing in ways that are consistent with the goal. You will become a true inspirations for the others and act confidently towards your goals.&lt;p&gt;The most important distinction that separates the successful and the non-successful is goal focus?&lt;p&gt;The people who define exactly what they want, who write detailed plans for achievement, and back those plans with persistence, are far more likely to succeed than those who do not.&lt;p&gt;This goal setting training course is designed for anyone who is looking to improve their ability to get the best from themselves and other people. You may be a manager or a non-manager.&lt;p&gt;Benefits of this Goal Setting training course:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will feel more confident to select your goals and targets&lt;li&gt;You will get the best possible from yourself and others because every action will be directed towards the desired goal&lt;li&gt;You will avoid all the perils and costs of having no goal- of being directionless&lt;li&gt;You will feel happier because you know that success means the realisation of your goal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one-day Goal Setting training courses is designed to cover the following areas:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop key skills in developing goal focus, communicating clearly, organizing people, prioritizing work, managing conflict and using self motivation&lt;li&gt;To provide clarity of purpose through clear vision, smart targets and standards&lt;li&gt;To communicate the goal with clarity and enthusiasm through using i.e. language, definitions and intelligent questioning&lt;li&gt;Goal achievement Training: The need to achieve goals can cause friction which can be beneficial or destructive depending on how it is managed. Proper conflict management is therefore important&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <start_time>2016-06-20 09:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-000235001-4</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/london-united-kingdom-/V0-001-000235001-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>London, United Kingdom</venue_name>
      <venue_display>0</venue_display>
      <venue_address>London, United Kingdom</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code>SW1</postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.5112139</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.1198244</longitude>
      <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-04-16 06:46:22</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-04-16 06:46:22</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image></image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
    <event id="E0-001-093368226-6">
      <title>Fincoder: Fintech Developer Conference, London 2016</title>
      <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/fincoder-fintech-developer-conference-london-2016-/E0-001-093368226-6?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
      <description> Join us for the 2nd Annual Fincoder: Fintech Developer Conference at Aviva&amp;#39;s Digital Garage in Hoxton Square. Developers, technologist, CTOs, technical co-founders and enterprise technology leaders in the financial services face unique challenges and opportunities.  Regulation, talent shortages, increased VC appetite and emerging technologies make it an interesting time to work in financial services technology. At Fincoder you&amp;#39;ll meet enterprise players, computer science graduates, start-ups, investors and other innovators in the space. Our second Fincoder event, part of London Tech Week, promised to be another exciting production. For the latest details visit, www.fincoder.co.cuk Fincoder London Agenda 09:00AM – 10:00AM Registration, Breakfast &amp; Networking Arrive early for a selection of breakfast nibbles, juices and warm drinks. Once you’re checked-in you’ll have time to meet other delegates and speakers. 10:00am – Introduction  A short welcome from the founders of Fincoder Luis Carranza, Founder, Fincoder &amp; Fintech Week 10:10am - 10:35am– What does Fintech Mean for Big Business A look at how bringing together lessons from other industries can have an impact on Fintech innovation. Pete Marsden, Digital CIO, Aviva 10:40am 11:05am– State of the Industry Learn about the current state of the Fintech industry and it’s trajectory for the near future. Ian has researched over 4,000 Fintech Companies and have been following the investment for several years. He&amp;#39;ll  present some of his findings. Ian Dowson, Principal, William Garrety Associates 11:10am - 11:30am – Fintech Developer Challenges An industry panel of experts from start-ups to enterprise discuss some of the unique challenges that face technical experts in the evolving world of financial services. Moderator, Donald Lawrence, Professor, UCL Rafal Zawadzki, CTO, Opportunity Network Mirko Puliafito, CTO - Eudata 11:35am 12:00pm–Fintech Intros from the Tech Team 12:05pm 12:20pm– The Chinese Opportunity Building bridges between Europe and China Bo Ji, Assistant Dean of Global Executive Education &amp; Chief Representative for Europe at Cheung Kong Graduate School of Business (CKGSB)   12:20 PM – 1:30 PM: Lunch Break &amp; Networking Session Enjoy a nice lunch while getting to know other attendees. 1:15pm - 1:40pm– Hiring, Retaining &amp; Nurturing Fintech Talent  Hiring and retaining tech talent in any industry has its challenges. We’ll look at how some of the brightest minds in the business attracting and keeping top talent. Nadia Edwards-Dashti, Founder and Financial IT Specialist at Harrington Starr Ryan Orton ,Head of Permanent, Emperic Amali de Alwis, CEO, Code First Girls 1:45pm - 2:05pm– The FCA and FinTech: help or hindrance?  We’ll look at the FCA’s Project Innovate, the regulatory sandbox and its approach to robo-advice. Celyn Armstrong, Counsel, Linklaters 2:10pm 2:35pm– Top Trends Panel, AI, IoT, Robo Advisory We’ll go beyond the buzz words and explore what some of the latest trends in Fintech mean in real life. Lior Nabat, CEO, Tradency,  Pritam Basu, Fintech Entrepreneur and Co-founder of Bank in a Box Luis Carranza, Blockchain Entreprenuer, co-founder iiota 2:35pm 2:45pm– Quick Break 2:45pm - 3:10pm – Live Hacking Demo A reminder to keep you and your customer’s data safe. Steven Smith, Founder,  Adarga 3:15pm -3:35pm– Blockchain: Beyond the POC  We’re starting to see blockchain companies going beyond proof of concept and into live market uses. Here from some of the companies that have gone beyond the hype. Calogero Scibetta, Operations, Everledger Kartik Natarajan, co-founder, Applied Blockchain 3:35pm - 3:55pm– Investor Message to Start-up CTOs  Nikita, Principal at Digital Space Ventures 3:55pm - 4:05pm– Visual Storytelling for Developers: A Reminder to Keep Things SimpleA lot of effort goes in to great code, but telling the story of the product/service you created is just as important to growing and gaining traction. Stefano Marrone, Founder, Nucco Brain 04:05 PM – 5:15 PM: Networking &amp; Refreshments A final chance to network and meet the day’s speakers and attendees.   </description>
      <start_time>2016-06-20 09:00:00</start_time>
      <stop_time></stop_time>
      <tz_id></tz_id>
      <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
      <tz_country></tz_country>
      <tz_city></tz_city>
      <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
      <venue_id>V0-001-009720345-7</venue_id>
      <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/aviva-digital-garage-/V0-001-009720345-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
      <venue_name>Aviva Digital Garage</venue_name>
      <venue_display>1</venue_display>
      <venue_address>33-35 Hoxton Square</venue_address>
      <city_name>London</city_name>
      <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
      <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
      <postal_code></postal_code>
      <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
      <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
      <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
      <latitude>51.501</latitude>
      <longitude>-0.124</longitude>
      <geocode_type>City Based GeoCodes</geocode_type>
      <all_day>0</all_day>
      <recur_string></recur_string>
      <calendar_count></calendar_count>
      <comment_count></comment_count>
      <link_count></link_count>
      <going_count></going_count>
      <watching_count></watching_count>
      <created>2016-05-13 12:46:31</created>
      <owner>evdb</owner>
      <modified>2016-06-17 03:58:59</modified>
      <performers></performers>
      <image>
        <thumb>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/48x48/other.jpg</url>
          <width>48</width>
          <height>48</height>
        </thumb>
        <medium>
          <url>http://s1.evcdn.com/store/skin/no_image/categories/128x128/other.jpg</url>
          <width>128</width>
          <height>128</height>
        </medium>
      </image>
      <privacy>1</privacy>
      <calendars></calendars>
      <groups></groups>
      <going></going>
      <categories>
        <category>
          <id>business</id>
          <name>Business &amp;amp; Networking</name>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </event>
  </events>
</search>